The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Given his temperament,
he won't forgive me for the bet we made earlier.
I have served the Sky Demon Country for centuries.
If I kill you,
the Demon Emperor will forgive me !
It's time for you to die !
Jin Wuxu,
what are you doing !?
How dare you !
Someone else is interfering ?
This power...
Could it be him ?
The 15th strike !
Back then, I prayed to the Ancient Demon in the Dragon Pool for years
before I could suppress my defying heart.
This guy dares to reach Ascendant through his own defying heart.
He's got some nerve.
Demon Spirit Land's Entrance\NEast Demon Spirit Sea\NPlanet Tian Yun
Divine Retribution !?
Who can summon such a tribulation !?
Blood Ancestor\NNirvana Cleanser
Why would a tribulation fall in the Demon Spirit Land ?
Xi Xue is still there !
Note: Yao Xixue's nickname
The tribulation in the East Demon Spirit Sea
is somehow affecting the fate of planet Tian Yun ?
It's a lightning tribulation...
If this kid survives it,
the law of the heavens
will have trouble dealing with his Ascendant cultivation.
No one can touch
my obsession !
I cultivated the Dao for 700 years
and somehow I keep encountering these tribulations !
Demonic Transformation !
Accept your fate and stay mortal
or defy it to become immortal !
If the heavens want to kill me...
then I will...
destroy the heavens !
He...
actually withstood the tribulation !
He turned celestial spiritual energy into demonic energy.
He's using his defying intent to resist the tribulation !
If I hadn't given up back then...
I wonder if I could be like him,
carving a path of cultivation where we defy the heavens.
The law of the heavens
will definitely not let this slide.
This is...
the Heaven's Might !
This kid is just reaching Ascendant through defiance.
Why would it summon a second tribulation ?
Could it be that his obsession
must absolutely be destroyed by the Heaven's Might !?
If that's the case...
the entire Sky Demon City will be buried with him !
Had I known...
I wouldn't have allowed him to undergo this tribulation.
The Heaven's Might is locked on him...
I can't move him...
It's coming !
Everyone,
evacuate immediately !
Run !
Hurry up !
The Heaven's Might is still increasing.
Venerable Ancestors,
please save the Sky Demon Country !
You little rascal,
Sky Demon Country's Ancestor
how long have I been in seclusion ?
The sky is already falling on us !
It's a long story,
save the population first !
Spatial Relocation !
You must leave this place for now.
I'm a descendant of the Ancient Demons
who transcended the law of the heavens.
This means I also am free from the law of the heavens !
Now,
let me test this shitty Divine Retribution !
The heavens can't shake my Dao Heart
so they will try to eradicate my existence !
They can destroy my body,
but they can't destroy
my Dao Heart !
No wonder they say that when the Heaven's Might acts,
no one is allowed to resist.
Its power is truly formidable...
Come !
Even if I die today,
even if my body turns to ashes,
even if my Dao is annihilated,
I will still...
hold on to my...
Dao.
Using a mortal body to resist the Heaven's Might...
Interesting.
For tens of thousands of years,
you're one of the few that chose to face the Heaven's Might.
Some were struck until their souls scattered.
Some became puppets of the law of the heavens.
But you...
actually carried your obsession
all the way to the Ascendant breakthrough.
Who are you ?
Countless years ago,
when the universe first formed,
there was a race born alongside the law of the heavens.
They called themselves the Ancient Order.
They drank Divine Retributions like wine,
stepped on the Heaven's Might like on stairs.
They were the world's first
Defiant Cultivators.
Later, the Ancient Order split into 3.
Those with extreme power called themselves Ancient Gods.
Those that walked the path of slaughter called themselves Ancient Devils.
And we...
who used Dao-destroying spells
are the Ancient Demons.
I am a strand of an Ancient Demon's soul.
There are 8 other strands like me in the other countries.
I have been trapped in the War Demon Drum for thousands of years.
But today, you awakened me with your defiant intent.
That is karma.
What do you want ?
It's simple.
I cannot stray too far from the War Demon Drum
so I need you
to get the other 8 soul strands from the other countries' sacred artifacts
and help me become a complete Ancient Demon.
Sky Demon
After all these years
I can't be the first Defiant Cultivator.
Why did you choose me ?
They can't withstand my power.
But you...
have the aura of an Ancient God within you.
Gods and Demons share the same origin
so you can withstand my power.
Why should I help you ?
Because I can help you survive the Heaven's Might !
I will help you.
I'll use your body
to fight back against the law of the heavens !
What do you think ?
This aura...
Soul, come back. We advance and retreat as one.
Divine Sense, come back. Don't fear the Heaven's Might.
Shared peril, shared resolve,
I'll make sure our voices converge to break the cycle.
Dao Destruction !
The war drum never stops,
We pay respects to the Ancestor !
it's summoning the Ancient Demon in my body.
Through the dust covered years,
who shared the pulse of the law of the heavens ?
Break free from the shackles and unite.
Defiance will beat the law of cause and effect.
This burning symbol
ignores its rusted outlines.
Listen to the fifteenth drumroll
as this roar cleanses the night.
We of the Ancient Order
The stars can be shattered
have never feared the Heaven's Might !
our clash rewrites the laws.
Time rewound, reversed,
the past has laid the groundwork for this moment.
Defying
Breakthrough !
Awaken me,
resonate in my veins.
My Divine Sense overlaps with the Demon Spirit's.
Their radiance intertwines and complements.
If one were to critique,
the distinction between good and evil is too flimsy.
You and I are together in our thoughts
whether we advance or retreat.
Defy conventions to shatter the laws.
Start strong by taking on this storm.
You and I, Demon and God fused,
are fighting together.
I'll break free of this karma step by step.
I'll turn the page of this tribulation by my own hand.
It's a dead end, yet also a breakthrough.
I choose when to move forward or retreat
as a Defiant Cultivator.
Soul, come back ! We advance and retreat together.
Fear not the wrath of the heavens, shatter the reincarnation cycle,
I'll accompany you.
The Ancient Demon Spirit between my eyebrows
How many years has it been...
is awakening.
The taste of these crimson clouds
Defying the sky, palms pressed together, forming a seal.
is still so delicious.
Shoulder to shoulder, defying the heavens' will.
Demon and God share my body,
together we move forward.
Shatter the heavens, the Dao's law, this tribulation.
What is there to fear in the Heaven's Might
when defying it ?
The tribulation...
has dispersed.
Meet me in 3 months
at the Dragon Pool.
I need to quickly find a place to cultivate in seclusion.
Where is he ?
Gu Yundun !
Sky Demon Country's\NSecond Ancestor
Come here !
Grandson is here.
That kid was chosen by the Ancestor.
We must bring him to the Dragon Pool alive.
Also,
you need to rebuild this place how it was before.
Grandson obeys.
Although my mental state is ready for Ascendant,
I still need to cultivate in seclusion to truly reach Ascendant.
Right now,
the celestial's cave is my best choice.
This is the first gift I give you,
an Ascendant Crystal.
It's useless to you now,
but if one day you are about to reach the Ascendant stage,
then it will help you.
If I succeed in reaching Ascendant today,
I promise to find a way to repay you, Senior.
To reach Ascendant,
one's Dao Heart must be complete.
Then, by using celestial spiritual energy as fuel,
the Dao Heart and the domain are refined together
until they fuse into one.
This...
is the legendary "Seeking the Dao in the morning".
During the fusion, origin energy is created.
This energy is extremely precious.
After the Celestial Realm emerged,
cultivators seeking immortality
made this origin energy their life energy.
Hence the saying:
"as long as they have a sliver of energy
the cultivators are immortal."
The Ascendant breakthrough
is the process of condensing origin energy into an Ascendant Crystal.
If successful,
the Ascendant Crystal becomes the heart of the Origin Soul.
The two fuse into one.
The Origin Soul becomes the domain,
the domain becomes the Origin Soul.
If it fails...
that's the death trial of Ascendant.
The celestial flame will turn the origin soul to dust.
This is...
"dying by the sunset".
This is bad !
Senior...
Let my crystallized obsession
help you
take this final step.
Thank you, Senior.
Ask
the perilous path filled with counless blades.
Can the mundane world be shattered
by a child's steadfast heart ?
If the laws of this world
10 years later
stand in the way,
I'll defy the universe to tread the heavens
and ask this question to the sky.
My heart's deepest wish
is to not kneel before these mountains and rivers.
Don't accept your doomed fate,
karma can be changed.
Unwilling to let go,
my obsessions propel me forward.
Don't be afraid.
Thunder trembles as I dare to tread through the reincarnation cycle.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
After 700 years of seeking the Dao...
Defying,
Wang Lin's avatar\NEarly stage Ascendant
I finally reached Ascendant.
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.
A lifetime's journey of defying
An Ascendant to subdue the heavens
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.
Mortals defy their fate to become immortal.\NThis obsession could shatter everything.
Qi Condensation
The path is shaped by the heart, the heart attains enlightenment, the Dao.\NHaving traversed every road ahead, I've never had fear of frost.
Foundation Establishment
Defying the heaven and the earth.\NCultivate the heart, have feelings, and these feelings will move heaven and earth.
Core Formation
Whether it's karma or fate,\NI will choose my path to Ascendant.
Nascent Soul
Keep these thoughts, and you will stay mortal.\NBreak through countless adversities, and you can become immortal.
The path is shaped by the heart, the heart attains enlightenment, the Dao.\NHaving traversed every road ahead, I've never had fear of frost.
Soul Formation
Soul Transformation
Ascendant
Defying the heaven and the earth.\NCultivate the heart, have feelings, and these feelings will move heaven and earth.
Whether it's karma or fate,\NI will choose my path to Ascendant.
My heart's deepest wish
is to not kneel before these mountains and rivers.
Don't accept your doomed fate,
karma can be changed.
Unwilling to let go,
my obsessions propel me forward.
Don't be afraid.
Thunder trembles as I dare to tread through the reincarnation cycle.
The Dao is indifferent
Accept your fate\Nand stay mortal\Nor defy it\Nto become immortal
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
Defy the heavens through your actions
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
Defy the heavens\Nby cultivating
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.
“The law of the heavens isn’t afraid of cultivators hiding, because once they hide, then their heart no longer contains the meaning of defying…”\N“What the law of the heaven is really afraid of is those who choose not to avoid but to face it… For those creatures, the heavens will do everything it can to erase them… You aren’t the first one, and you won’t be the last…”\N“When others face Ascendant, they either follow the law of the heavens or avoid it, so divine retribution doesn’t arrive. Yet you chose to face it, and that caused the divine retribution to descend…”\N\N[...]\N\NAt the moment the Ascendant Crystal is formed, you might feel like you have become nothing and your soul is wandering the heavens and earth. This feeling is extremely rare and it is called Ascendant Enlightenment.\NNormally, the first thing cultivators on a cultivation planet do is use this moment of comprehension to pull their soul strand back from the Cultivation Planet Crystal. Although the chance is only 50%, they must try !\NWang Lin had already recovered his soul strand, so he obviously didn’t need to do this. At this moment, all of the celestial jades in his bag had already been placed around him. The last bit of celestial spiritual energy had just been squeezed out from the jade before they turned to dust.\N\NThere was a fire storm raging inside Wang Lin as his body underwent earth-shattering changes. His origin soul was like a giant cocoon, his domain was the life inside the cocoon, and the celestial spiritual energy was the raging fire outside the cocoon !\N"Seeking the Dao in the morning only to die by the sunset" is something every Ascendant cultivator knows, and it has a lot to do with this flame. If one can’t get past this trial, then this flame will go from ethereal to real and will burn the origin soul and body to dust in an instant !
What a sweet and delicious aura...
The origin energy of a newborn Ascendant
is like a freshly opened bottle of wine.